I’m sure we all have childhood memories – what we did at school, the food we ate, the games we played.
我相信每个人都有属于自己的童年回忆——上学时的趣事、吃过的美食、玩过的游戏。
But perhaps the most vivid recollections are those of the toys we played with.
但或许最鲜活的记忆，是那些陪伴我们成长的玩具。
There were many gadgets that may seem unsophisticated now but were the must-have items in the playground back in the day.
有许多小玩意儿如今看来可能显得简陋，但在当年的操场上，它们可是人手必备的热门单品。
Now it seems that our passion for nostalgia means some of them are making a comeback.
而现在，人们对怀旧情怀的热衷，让其中一些玩具正重新流行起来。
One of my favourites was the Nintendo Game Boy, which returned to the shops last year, 30 years after it was first released.
我最喜欢的玩具之一就是任天堂的Game Boy掌上游戏机。这款产品在发布30年后，于去年重返市场。
This handheld console has had some modifications, but still offers a simple gaming experience and a trip down memory lane!
它的掌机外观做了些许改良，但依旧能带来简单纯粹的游戏体验，让人重温往昔时光！
If the Game Boy wasn’t from your era, how about the Tamagotchi?
如果Game Boy不属于你的童年时代，那电子宠物鸡呢？
This egg-shaped, plastic pet that its owner had to keep ‘alive’ with constant care and attention - was the must-have item not long after its launch in 1996.
这款鸡蛋形状的塑料宠物玩具需要玩家必须悉心照料才能让它“存活”下去，于1996年推出后不久就成了爆款。
These sometimes annoying ‘creatures’ were such a distraction in the classroom, they often got banned from school.
这些有时会惹人烦的“小家伙”在教室分散学生们的注意力，因此常常被学校禁止带入。
But now, childlike adults can relive their wasted youth because Japanese manufacturer Bandai will soon release an all-colour, new-and-improved version of the classic toy.
但如今，童心未泯的成年人可以重拾逝去的青春了——日本制造商万代即将推出这款经典玩具的全新彩色升级版。
Its maker says it’s evolved from a pet into more of a character, and can inhabit different lands, as well as get married and breed.
制造商表示，新款电子宠物鸡不再只是一个宠物，更像是一个角色，它可以居住在不同的场景中，还能结婚生子。
So what’s driving this demand for retro goods?
那么，是什么催生了人们对复古商品的需求呢？
Retail Analyst for Mintel, Chana Baram, told the BBC people are searching for comfort in 'the good old days'.
英敏特零售分析师钱娜·巴拉姆向英国广播公司表示，人们正从“往昔的美好时光”中寻求慰藉。
Certainly, playing with an old toy brings back memories of our formative years and gives us a feel-good factor, but it’s also something brands and marketing companies want to cash in on.
诚然，把玩旧玩具能唤起我们成长时期的回忆，带来愉悦的心情，但这也是各大品牌和营销公司想要从中牟利的商机。
Retro toys are also something we could cash in on too.
我们普通人也可以从复古玩具中获益。
In the darkest corners of many attics and spare rooms lie the toys of Christmas past.
许多家庭的阁楼和闲置房间的角落里，都藏着当年圣诞节收到的玩具。
And those once much-loved and played with presents may now have a value beyond nostalgia.
这些曾经备受喜爱的礼物，如今的价值或许早已超越了怀旧本身。
Toyologist Peter Jenkinson told the BBC that any number of "toys that we all played with as kids are now worth more than a few quid".
玩具专家彼得·詹金森向英国广播公司透露，“我们小时候玩过的很多玩具，现在都价值不菲”。
He suggests there’s a real collectors' market for certain old board games, Star Wars characters, Sindy dolls and Lego sets.
他指出，一些老式棋盘游戏、星球大战人物模型、仙蒂娃娃和乐高套装，在收藏市场上十分走俏。
However, if you own something like this, it may be just too precious to sell, and part with the connection to your childhood.
不过，如果你也珍藏着这样的玩具，它或许会因为承载着童年的回忆而太过珍贵，让你舍不得出售，不愿割舍这份与童年的联结。